Guide to the Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records, 1958-2000.
Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records
- Series IV Projects
  - Filming
    - Filming Project Agreements, 2004-2007 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Michael Goldenberg's Screen Play Script, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Visitor Center
    - Visitor Center Project, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Visitor Center Funding, 1990-1995 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Visitor Center Funding, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Visitor Center Funding, 1991-2010 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Visitor Center Contracts, 1993-1997 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Visitor Center Ground Breaking, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Visitor Center Construction, 1990-1997 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Visitor Center Construction Correspondence, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Visitor Center Artist Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Visitor Center Dedication, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Science Teacher Workshops, 1997-2000 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Public Education and Outreach, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - First Upgrade Project
    - Ammann & Whitney
      - Feasibility Study & Concept Development for Upgrading of Suspended Antenna Structure, 8/72 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Report on Inspection of Cable System, 9/72 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Proposal for Consulting Engineering Services, Phase I, 2/72 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Survey of Suspended Structure & Reflector Cable Anchorages, 8/72 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Test Report on Hanger G-2, 3/73 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Varian/Continental Elec.
      - Installation & Operation of the Varian X3070A 450 kW Klystron Amplifier, March 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6A)
      - Test Data X-3070A High Power Klystron Amplifier, 6/24/74 (Box 26, Folder 6B)
    - Continental Elec. Contracts, 1972-84 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Environmental Protection Agency Regulation, 2/75 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Los Canos Status Report on 100-ft Diameter Interferometer Project - Los Canos, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Instructions, Arecibo Superstructure Analysis Program for use on IBM System/370 (Model 168) Computer at Cornell, 6/75 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Sweo Engineering Final Report, Drive & Control Upgrading Study, May 1977 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Solar TurbinesSubcontract for overhaul & repair, 1/80 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - 1971 First Upgrade Construction Schedule (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - E-Systems Reflector Upgrade
      - Pre-Contract Correspondence, 11/71 (Box 26, Folder 14A)
      - Chronology of CU/E-Systems Contract Close-out, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 14B)
    - TAM Soil Study, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - S-Band Transmitter RFP
      - Request for Proposal, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Pre-Qualification & other correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Pre-Qualification documents, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Pre-Qualification & other correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Continental Electronics - S-Band
      - S-Band Transmitter Preliminary Design, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Technical Proposal for a High Power S-Band Radar Transmitter, Mar 1973 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Invitation for Bids Site Work Special Tasks Arecibo, Oct 1973 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - RFP & Bid Process, 1972-73 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Proposal Review, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Subcontract Price Proposal for a High Power S-Band Radar Transmitter, 3-5-73 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - S-Band Transmitter Final Reports, Feb 1973 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Ammann & Whitney On-site Review of Upgrading Elevation Railway, 9/73 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - S-Band budget, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Pre-Construction Corres., 1984-1992 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Consultants, 1983-84 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Surface mapping/alignment, 1983-84 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Support letters, 1989-90 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Tor Hagfors Reports Upgrade Program Reports, 1984-85, Hagfors (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Colin Hines Reports & Corres., 1988, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Cable Structure, 1980-89 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Organization Charts, 1989-93 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Second Upgrading Proposals & Appendices, 1985, 1987
      - Proposal for Phase 1 of an Arecibo Upgrading Program, Mar 1986 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Proposal for Second Arecibo Upgrading, Phase 1 Appendices (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Proceedings of the Arecibo Upgrading Workshop, Cornell University, October 1986 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Proposal for Second Arecibo Upgrading, Phase 2, Dec 1987 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Proposal for Second Arecibo Upgrading, Phase 2 Appendices (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Pre-Upgrading Meeting Minutes, Feb 1984 - Nov 1987 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Upgrading Workshops, 1986-93
      - Meeting of the Scientific Beneifts of an Upgrade Arecibo Observatory, Oct 1986 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Paul Stetson Vugraphs-Upgrading Workshop, Oct 1986 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Arecibo Upgrading Workshop, Feb 1990 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Pre-Construction Meeting, Apr 1993 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Project Funding-Cornell & Puerto Rico, 1989-92
      - Puerto Rican Gov't Funding, 1989-92 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Cornell funds, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Site Land Ownership Materials (ARPE), 7/92 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Instrumentation Development Plan - R.G. Davenport (no date) (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Upgrade Management, 1989-91
      - Management discussions, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      - Program Manager Search, 6/90 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Environmental Impact, 1991-95
      - NSF Environmental Impact on Proposed Upgrading, 4/91 (Box 27, Folder 30)
      - Puerto Rico Environmental Quality Board Regulation for the Control of Atmospheric Pollution, 9/95 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Second Upgrade Project, Gregorian Feed
    - Planning/Design Task Group Meetings, 1990-1996
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Feb 1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Oct 1990 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Dec 1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Feb 1991 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Mar 1991 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, May 1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, July 1991 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Aug 1991 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Nov 1991 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Jan 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Mar 1992 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, May 1992 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, July 1992 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Oct 1992 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Jan 1993 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Mar 1993 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, May 1993 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, July 1993 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Sep 1993 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Dec 1993 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Feb 1994 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Apr 1994 (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, June 1994 (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Oct 1994 (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Jan 1995 (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Mar 1995 (Box 28, Folder 26)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes,June 1995 (Box 28, Folder 27)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Aug 1995 (Box 28, Folder 28)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Oct 1995 (Box 28, Folder 29)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Jan 1996 (Box 28, Folder 30)
      - Upgrade: Planning/Design Task Group Meeting Minutes, Mar 1996 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Other Upgrade Meetings, 1992-1997
      - Progress/Project Meeting Minutes - Technical & Business Sessions, 1992-94 (Box 28, Folder 32)
      - Progress/Project Meeting Minutes - Technical & Business Sessions, 1995-94 (Box 28, Folder 33)
      - Misc. Meeting Minutes, 1993-95 (Box 28, Folder 34)
      - Weekly Site Reports Apr 1994 -Feb 1997, Report #1-2, 4-5, 7-8, 10-11, 14-17, 22-25, 28-29, 31, 33-35, 42-44, 46-69, 72-75, 78, 94-101, 103-105, 110-122, 145-151 (Box 28, Folder 35)
      - RSI/Arecibo Site Meeting Minutes, #23-25 (Nov'93), #28-62 (Jan'94-Jan'95) (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Weekly Schedule Review Meeting Minutes, Mar 1995-Apr 1997 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Radio Astronomy Group Upgrade Coordination Meetings, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Maldonado Weekly Reports, 1999-2002 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Punch Lists, 1995-97 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Arecibo Upgrade Notes, Feb 1993 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Task Reports, 1996-97 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Structural Upgrading Schedules, 1991-94 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Ammann & Whitney (A&W) Contracts, 1986, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - HOOGHOUT (Project Engr) FILES, 1986-1994
      - Ammann & Whitney Correspondence, 1991-93 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Mike Davis Correspondence, 1992-94 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Evan Kurtz-Transmitter Correspondence, 1992-94 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - CBD (Commercial Business Daily) ads, 1991-92 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - S-Band Transmitter - Continental Electronics, 1993-94 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Hooghout Upgrade Notes, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Hooghout file - Contractor Qualifications, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - GBT - Green Bank Telescope Corres., 1992-93 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - NAIC Lab, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Lynn Baker - Reflectors, 1992-94 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Upgrade Correspondence: NAIC Ithaca to Arecibo, 1993-1997
      - Samuelson/Hooghoudt to Maldonado/Site, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Samuelson/Hooghoudt to Maldonado/Site, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Samuelson/Hooghoudt to Maldonado/Site, 1995-97 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Upgrade Correspondence: NAIC Ithaca to RSI
      - Samuelson/Hooghoudt to RSI, 1993-1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Samuelson/Hooghoudt to RSI, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Upgrade Correspondence: Arecibo to NAIC Ithaca
      - Maldonado/Site to Samuelson/Hooghoudt, 1992-94 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Maldonado/Site to Samuelson/Hooghoudt, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Maldonado/Site to Samuelson/Hooghoudt, 1996-97 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Upgrade Correspondence: Arecibo to RSI
      - Maldonado/Site to RSI, 1993-94 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Maldonado/Site to RSI, 1995-97 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Upgrade Corres: RSI to Arecibo RSI to Maldonado/Site, 1994-97 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Upgrade Correspondence: RSI to NAIC Ithaca
      - RSI to Samuelson/Hooghout, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - RSI to Samuelson/Hooghout, Jan-May 1994 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - RSI to Samuelson/Hooghout, June-Dec 1994 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - RSI to Samuelson/Hooghout, Jan-June 1995 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - RSI to Samuelson/Hooghout, July-Dec 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - RSI to Samuelson/Hooghout, Jan-Mar 1996 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - RSI to Samuelson/Hooghout, Apr-Dec 1996 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - RSI to Samuelson/Hooghout, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Upgrade Corres: Between RSI & Cornell Contracts Mgmt, 1992-97 Between RSI & Cornell Contracts Management, 1992-97 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Upgrade Corres: RSI Construction Accidents, 1993-96 RSI Construction Accidents, 1993-96 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Upgrade Correspondence: RSI to Ammann & Whitney, 1993-1997
      - RSI to Ammann & Whitney, 1993-94 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - RSI to Ammann & Whitney, 1995-97 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Upgrade Corres: Ammann & Whitney to RSI, 1993-96 Ammann & Whitney to RSI, 1993-96 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Ammann & Whitney - Other (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Upgrade Correspondence: Between Ammann & Whitney & NAIC Ithaca, 1991-1998
      - Ammann & Whitney to NAIC Ithaca, 1991, 1994-98 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - NAIC Ithaca to Ammann & Whitney, 1993-97 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Upgrade Correspondence: Between Ammann & Whitney & Arecibo, 1992-2003
      - Ammann & Whitney to Site/Maldonado, 1992-97 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Site/Maldonado to Ammann & Whitney, 1992-2003 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Upgrade Correspondence: Interoffice Memos
      - Arecibo Interoffice Memos, 1992-97 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - NAIC Ithaca Interoffice Memos, 1992-97 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Arecibo to NAIC Ithaca memos, 1993-96 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - NAIC Ithaca to Arecibo memos, 1992-97 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Letters to House Appropriations Subcommittee, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Exemption from Excise Taxes for Upgrading Contractor's Materials, 1992-92 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Gregorian Feed - General
      - Dunn & Bradstreet - Supplier Evaluations Jan 10, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - General Correspondence, 1986-87, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Upgrading Budgets, 1991-94 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Pre-Qualification, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Facilities Management, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Contractors, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Scientific/Technical Reports, 1985-1996 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Structural Reinforcement, 1991-1992
      - General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Ammann & Whitney discussion of presentation, May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Pre-Proposal Documents, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Pre-Bid Conference, Sept 1992 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Technical Evaluation of Bidding Proposals, Nov 1992 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Structural Reinforcement Schedules, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Per-Simon Kildal Consulting, 1985 Gregorian Feed Design Consulting Agreement, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Cirrus Consulting - Per-Simon Kildal, 1991-1992
      - Consulting Agreement - general correspondence, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Progress Reports, 1991-92 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Final Report, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Pre-proposal Documents, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Kildal Antenna Consulting, 1991-1994
      - Engineering Service Agreement, 4/91 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Pre-Proposal Documents, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Invoices and Payments, 1991-92 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Engineering Service Agreement, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Kildal Technical Memos, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Fracture Analysis Consultants, 1991-1997
      - Proposal, PO, Final Report, 1991-93 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - Final Report on the Structural Analysis of the Existing & Proposed Hangers for the Arecibo Ring Girder, 7-22-92 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Measurement of the Structural Response of a New Ring-Girder Hanger at the Arecibo Observatory-Final Report, 8/93 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Fracture & Fatigue Analyses of Damaged Hairpin Rod, 3/3/97 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Arecibo research activities requiring use of a hydrogen maser frequency standard, Leonid Gurvits, 7/92 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Azimuth Drive Systems, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Galindo Associates, 1992-1994
      - Proposal for services, 2/92 (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Galindo PO for diffraction analyses study of final design of 3 reflector antenna & feed system 9/94 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - Invoices and Payments, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Pre-Proposal Documents, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Timothy Bond, 1993 Strain gage measurements on azimuth hangers, Feb 1993 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Bill McGuire, 1996 Consulting Agreement - cable tensioning problem, 7/96 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Gregorian Upgrade Progress Reports, 1991-92 Feb 1991 - Mar 1992 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - TIW Systems, 1989-1992
      - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 36)
      - Invoices and Payments, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 37)
      - Engineering Service Agreement, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - Final Report - Arecibo Upgrade Study, 1-3-90 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Paul Stetson, 1984-1993
      - Progress Report, Gregorian Feed System, 1-11-85 (Box 32, Folder 40)
      - Revised Feed Arm Blockage & Feed Platform Blockage data, Sep 1993 (Box 32, Folder 41)
      - Stetson - Upgrade Corres., 1984-85 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Pratt Institute earthquake study, 1986-1987
      - General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Subcontract, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Report on Earthquake effects on supporting towers, Nov 1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ESSCO (Electronics Space Systems Corp), 1985 General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Radome wind tunnel study, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Richard D'Amato Engineering Services, 1985 Radome analysis study, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Univ. Arizona, 1986 Reflector milling, Sep 1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Flam & Russell Inc., 1986 Antenna positioner for mini-Gregorian feed, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Report on the Project of Earthquake Related Upgrading of Tower 8 Support at the Arecibo Observatory, Dr. Mikolaj Wegrzyn, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Arecibo Observatory Photogrammetric Survey Agmt, 1/91 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Anchor Cable 8-2 Report, 1/92 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Radiation Systems, Inc. 1992-1995
      - RSI Contract 1992 (1 of 2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - RSI Contract 1992 (2 of 2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - RSI/UAD Contract documents & corres., 1992-95 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - RSI/UAD Administration, 1993-1995
      - Proposal for Alternate 2 Azimuth Rail Installation and Alternate 3 Tower Reinforcing, Rev A 8-5-93 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Schedule of Values, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Corres. Bill Terry, RSI Program Manager 1993 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Discipline: schedule delays, excavation safety plan, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Subcontractor correspondence, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - RSI use of GFE equipment, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - RSI/UAD General, 1993-1995
      - Cornell Facilities Management correspondence, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - General Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Internal NAIC-Ithaca correspondence, 1993-95 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Bob Matyas, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - RSI/UAD Arecibo Activity
      - Memos to Arecibo 1992-93 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Memos from Arecibo, 1992-93 (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Site accidents, 1993-96 (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - Site meetings, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 28)
      - Progress Reports, May-Oct 1993 (Box 33, Folder 29)
      - Memos from Maldonado to RSI/UAD, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 30)
      - Meetings with RSI/UAD, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - RSI CQC Field Modification Reports, 1993, 1996-97 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - COMSAT/RSI Status Reports
      - Briefing on Status of Gregorian Upgrade, Nov 1994 (Box 33, Folder 33)
      - Follow-up Briefing on Status of Gregorian Upgrade, Nov 1994 (Box 33, Folder 34)
      - Briefing on Status of Gregorian Upgrade, Feb 1995 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Wind tunnel tests, Aug 1993 & Corres., 1994 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Temcor-RSI -- Dome
      - Corres. Temcor-RSI, 1993, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 37)
      - Selection of Temcor; company information 1993 (Box 33, Folder 38)
      - Temcor - Dome design, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 39)
      - Temcor - Dome Assembly, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Gregorian Feed - Proposal Process
      - RSI/UAD Contractor Quality Control (CQC) System Quality Assurance Plan, Revision A, 6/93 (Box 33, Folder 41)
      - Clarification Meeting, 01/25/93 (Box 33, Folder 42)
      - Clarification Meeting, 12/08/93 (Box 33, Folder 43)
      - Contract negotiations, 12/31/92 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Contract negotiations, 1/01-31/93 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Contract negotiations, 2/01/93 Signing (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Proposal Evaluation, Nov 1992 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Evaluation & Clarification Meeting, 12-8-92 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - General, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Sponsored Programs, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Civil Works Bid Briefing, 2-11-93 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Contractors, 1987, 1994-1996
      - F& M MAFGO, Hoist rental, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Neal S. Morton & Associates, Weld inspections, 1994 & 1995 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Reynolds Aluminum Supply, Aluminum I-Beam purchase, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Maxwell Bennett Assoc., Compressive load cell/connector, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - IMTEC, Tertiary panel measurement equipment, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Advanced Design Consulting, Cable drag assembly, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Griffin Gear, Rotary floor rack gear, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Carrier Corp, Air conditioners, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - RSI Future C.O., WBS budget worksheet, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Rotary floor hardware, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Graham Gear, Reduction gear, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Feed module rack gear, Request for estimates, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Machine Tool Svcs, Rack gear, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - TODCO, Panels for rotary floor - P.O., 1995 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Advanced Design Consulting, Feed module rack adjustment, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - BMIL International, Bally electronics shelter, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - Finger Lakes Fabricating, Feed module rotary floor drive system, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - Steel & Welding Insection, Dome & Feed Module, Mar 1996 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - Steel Structures Tech Ctr, electroplating A325 bolts, Nov 1994 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Taitem Engineering, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Geodetic Services, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Geotec, soil conditions around anchor blocks, 1993-94 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - CU Civil & Environmental Engineering, Seismic Update, Feb 1994 (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Ortiz Suarez Subsoil Exploration Report, 10-28-87 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Other contractors (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Builder's Risk Insurance, 1991-92 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - A.O. Site preparations, Facilities working roads, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - RSI Invoices, Payments, Schedules
      - Monthly reports for request for payments, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - Project schedules, Aug 1993-Oct 1996 (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - Schedule of Values, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - RSI Invoices/Payments #1-8, 1993-95 (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - RSI Invoices/Payments #9-17, 1995-97 (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - Cash flow, COMSAT-RSI payments, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - RSI/UAD Change Orders
      - General, 1994-96 (Box 34, Folder 42)
      - Change Order Logs, 1993-94 (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - Change Order #1,Azimuth Rail, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - Change Order #2, Tower Reinforcing, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - Change Order #3, Wind Tunnel Test, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 46)
      - Change Order #4, B4 Modification, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 47)
      - Change Order #5, Increase in Boom Length, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 48)
      - Change Order #6, B-8 Retaining Wall, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 49)